export const questions = [
  {
    question: "3+5",
    correctAnswer: "8",
    wrongAnswer: "7",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "7*9",
    correctAnswer: "63",
    wrongAnswer: "56",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "12-7",
    correctAnswer: "5",
    wrongAnswer: "6",
    level: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "73-19",
    correctAnswer: "54",
    wrongAnswer: "56",
    level: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "8*6",
    correctAnswer: "48",
    wrongAnswer: "42",
    level: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "12+39",
    correctAnswer: "51",
    wrongAnswer: "58",
    level: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "121 / 11",
    correctAnswer: "11",
    wrongAnswer: "12",
    level: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "33+48",
    correctAnswer: "81",
    wrongAnswer: "72",
    level: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "132 - 85",
    correctAnswer: "47",
    wrongAnswer: "55",
    level: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "",
    correctAnswer: "",
    wrongAnswer: "",
    level: 0,
  },
];
